

# Contacts

Phone: +48 725 135 671 E-mail: maniaorwat@gmail.com

## Tech skills and tools

- Salesforce: Sales Cloud /
  Salesforce Inspector,
  Salesforce Workbench
- HTML & CSS
- PostgreSQL / PGAdmin
- GIT / Bitbucket
- REST API / Postman
- TestLink
- Jira

## **Currently learning**

- Selenium Webdriver
- Cypress

# Soft skills

- Agile & Scrum
- Proficient in English & French
- Good communicator
- Teamwork

DOWNLOAD THIS RESUME

SEE CODE FOR THIS PAGE

# Anna-Maria Orwat

# QA specialist

If I was to describe my approach to professional life, I would say: take opportunities and make the best out of them.

My tech career path began unconventionally - I was working on a software project on the client's/business side, and then I was taken over by my current development team as their new QA.

I now have 18 months of QA experience under my belt - never looked back since!

# **Employment history**

#### Software tester at DAC Software Polska

December 2019 - up to now

- Defining test scenarios based on business requirements
- Conducting manual tests (UI, integration, other)
- Taking active part in feature design process
- Supporting the development team as a Scrum Master

## Backoffice coordinator at Qarson Services Sp. z o.o.

Apil 2018 - November 2019

- Managing a team of 5-6 people
- Preparing and executing introductory training programs
- Creating current reports
- Following French administrational laws (automotive field)
- Creating and adjusting procedures

## Administration specialist at Qarson Services Sp. z o.o.

October 2017 - April 2018

- Administrational handling of current orders
- French customer service (written and spoken)
- Cooperation with other departments (optimising procedures)

## Junior Administration specialist at Qarson Services Sp. z o.o.

March 2017 - October 2018

# Education

### Professional Scrum Master I, Scrum.org | CERTIFICATE

September 2020

Certified Scrum Master course, ATUM Sp. z o.o.

September 2020

ISTQB Foundation Level | CERTIFICATE

August 2020

"Become a Tester", Sii Training Practice | CERTIFICATE

June 2020 - July 2020